[
    {
        "comment": "Abelardo Gonzales I am in San Antonio and I still can not login.",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Abelardo Gonzales I am",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "San Antonio",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Makinu Fox Cat is anyone having issues paying with their card online?",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Fox Cat",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Rod munch live in florida where hurricaine is hitting",
        "sentiment_score": 0.13636363636363635,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "florida",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Rod munch Online Banking is temporarily unavailable",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [],
        "classifications": [
            "online banking"
        ]
    },
    {
        "comment": "Rod munch yea Online Banking is temporarily unavailable",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [],
        "classifications": [
            "online banking"
        ]
    },
    {
        "comment": "Kim Marasti can&#x27;t log in to app, says unavailable...anyone else?",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Kim Marasti can&#x27;t",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Glizzy Anyone get their direct deposit yet?",
        "sentiment_score": 0.1,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Glizzy Anyone",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": [
            "direct deposit"
        ]
    },
    {
        "comment": "Glizzy Nope",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Glizzy",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Daniel Any get early pay yet?",
        "sentiment_score": 0.1,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Daniel Any",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Ihop We have a problem. Please try again a little later. when using zelle what is wrong with the browser?????",
        "sentiment_score": -0.22916666666666666,
        "sentiment": "negative",
        "entities": [
            [
                "a little later",
                "DATE"
            ],
            [
                "zelle",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": [
            "Zelle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "comment": "ANonymous Ok, thanks. Just wanted to see if I was the only one with this issue.",
        "sentiment_score": 0.2333333333333333,
        "sentiment": "positive",
        "entities": [
            [
                "ANonymous Ok",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Jeff R Yes",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Jeff",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Jeff R Still no deposit, Still waiting. Of course Wells Fargo states Early Direct Deposit is not gauranteed...",
        "sentiment_score": 0.1,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Jeff",
                "PERSON"
            ],
            [
                "Wells Fargo",
                "ORG"
            ],
            [
                "Early Direct Deposit",
                "ORG"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": [
            "direct deposit"
        ]
    },
    {
        "comment": "ANonymous Anybody else missing their early deposit? It&#x27;s an hour after the normal deposit time and I haven&#x27;t seen anything yet.",
        "sentiment_score": 0.016666666666666663,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "ANonymous Anybody",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "eric me either says unavailable I guess I will wait",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "eric",
                "PERSON"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Tryse Can’t use app to mobile deposit",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [],
        "classifications": []
    },
    {
        "comment": "Verria-Nichole Can&#x27;t make credit card payments. Not even the transactions will load.",
        "sentiment_score": 0.0,
        "sentiment": "neutral",
        "entities": [
            [
                "Verria",
                "GPE"
            ]
        ],
        "classifications": [
            "credit card"
        ]
    }
]